{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Asbestos Siding Removal Contractors","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40414/":{"taskOID":40414,"originalTaskOID":40414,"setID":706,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":1079,"questionDisplayText":"Visible Symptoms","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"List any visible symptoms.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6316,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"There's a leak through the wall","answerDisplayText":"There's a leak through the wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5692,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Siding panel is loose or hanging out of position","answerDisplayText":"Siding panel is loose or hanging out of position","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5693,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Siding panel is missing","answerDisplayText":"Siding panel is missing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5694,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Siding panel is warped, cracked or split","answerDisplayText":"Siding panel is warped, cracked or split","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5684,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Siding crumbles into powdery dust","answerDisplayText":"Siding crumbles into powdery dust","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3873,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Missing, broken or rusty flashing","answerDisplayText":"Missing, broken or rusty flashing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1820,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Damaged soffit or fascia","answerDisplayText":"Damaged soffit or fascia","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3845,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Mildew or fungus grows on siding","answerDisplayText":"Mildew or fungus grows on siding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":8,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":1079,"questionDisplayText":"Visible Symptoms","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"List any visible symptoms.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6316,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"There's a leak through the wall","answerDisplayText":"There's a leak through the wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5692,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Siding panel is loose or hanging out of position","answerDisplayText":"Siding panel is loose or hanging out of position","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5693,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Siding panel is missing","answerDisplayText":"Siding panel is missing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5694,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Siding panel is warped, cracked or split","answerDisplayText":"Siding panel is warped, cracked or split","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5684,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Siding crumbles into powdery dust","answerDisplayText":"Siding crumbles into powdery dust","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3873,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Missing, broken or rusty flashing","answerDisplayText":"Missing, broken or rusty flashing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1820,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Damaged soffit or fascia","answerDisplayText":"Damaged soffit or fascia","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3845,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Mildew or fungus grows on siding","answerDisplayText":"Mildew or fungus grows on siding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":6316,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"There's a leak through the wall","answerDisplayText":"There's a leak through the wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5692,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Siding panel is loose or hanging out of position","answerDisplayText":"Siding panel is loose or hanging out of position","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5693,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Siding panel is missing","answerDisplayText":"Siding panel is missing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5694,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Siding panel is warped, cracked or split","answerDisplayText":"Siding panel is warped, cracked or split","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5684,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Siding crumbles into powdery dust","answerDisplayText":"Siding crumbles into powdery dust","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3873,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Missing, broken or rusty flashing","answerDisplayText":"Missing, broken or rusty flashing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1820,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Damaged soffit or fascia","answerDisplayText":"Damaged soffit or fascia","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3845,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Mildew or fungus grows on siding","answerDisplayText":"Mildew or fungus grows on siding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":8,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/40414/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40414,"taskName":"Asbestos Siding - Repair","taskDescription":"Repair Asbestos Siding","xmTaskDescriptor":"Asbestos Siding Removal Contractors","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":12,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Asbestos exterior maintenance stone world","textMessagingName":"Repr Asbestos","rolloverLongDesc":"While not generally installed anymore, many older homes have asbestos shingles. These firms know how to work with the brittle shingles. Note separate category for asbestos removal.","rolloverShortDesc":"Overlapping, brittle shingles.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Repair Asbestos Siding.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Asbestos Siding Removal \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Replace Asbestos Siding","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":69,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Asbestos Siding Repair","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Asbestos Siding - Repair","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Asbestos Siding Repair Project","urlName":"Asbestos-Siding-Repair","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Asbestos Siding Removal Pros - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor Reviews \u0026 Costs","searchKeywords":"Asbestos,exterior,maintenance,stone,world,material,roofing,eliminate,Siding,removal,concrete","emcCategoryOid":-12064,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":706,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}